<resources>
    <string name="app_name">H2gether</string>

    <string name="about_us_text">Welcome to H2gether, your reliable companion for staying hydrated throughout the day. Developed by a team of four dedicated computer engineering students at Polytechnic University of the Philippines (PUP) Sta. Mesa Manila, H2gether is designed to help you maintain a healthy water intake and promote overall well-being. \n\nAt H2gether, our mission is to make a positive difference in the lives of our users by promoting healthy hydration habits. We believe that staying hydrated is essential for maintaining optimal physical and mental performance. By delivering timely reminders and personalized water intake recommendations, we aim to empower individuals to prioritize their hydration needs and make informed choices about their well-being. \n\nRemember, with H2gether by your side, you\'ll never miss a sip!</string>

    <string name="disclaimer_text">Disclaimer: H2gether is not a substitute for professional medical advice. Please consult your healthcare provider for personalized hydration recommendations.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Effective Date: July XX, 2023 \n\nWe at SkyLark are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and maintaining the confidentiality of the information you provide to us. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, disclose, and protect your personal information when you use our Water Reminder Mobile App, H2gether. By using the App, you consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. \n\nCollection of Personal Information \n1.1 Account Creation: When you create an account on our App, we collect personal information such as your email address, password, or, alternatively, your Google account information. \n1.2 Personal Information: To provide personalized features and functionality, we may collect additional personal information such as sex, age, height, weight, and activity level. This information is used to calculate personalized water intake recommendations. \n1.3 Water Intake Progress: We collect and store data regarding your water intake progress to track and provide insights into your hydration habits. \n1.4 Weather Integration: The App may integrate with third-party weather services to retrieve current temperature information based on your location. This information is used to provide weather-related insights and recommendations for your hydration. \n\nUse of Personal Information \n2.1 Account Management: We use your personal information to manage and authenticate your account and to provide you with access to the features and functionality of the App. \n2.2 Personalized Water Intake Plan: Your personal information, including sex, age, height, weight, and activity level, is used to calculate personalized water intake recommendations. \n2.3 Water Intake Tracking: We use the information about your water intake progress to track and display your hydration levels, provide reminders, and offer insights to help you stay hydrated. \n2.4 Weather Integration: The current temperature information retrieved from third-party weather services is used to enhance your experience by displaying weather-related insights and recommendations. \n\nDisclosure of Personal Information \n3.1 Service Providers: We may engage third-party service providers who assist us in providing the App. These service providers have access to your personal information only to perform tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. \n3.2 Legal Requirements: We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in response to a valid request from a governmental authority. \n\nData Security \nWe implement reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, or alteration. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee absolute security. \n\nChildren\'s Privacy \nThe App is not intended for use by individuals under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us, and we will take steps to remove the information. \n\nYour Choices \nYou can access, update, or delete your personal information by accessing the profile and settings pages within the App. You may also contact us to exercise your rights or request assistance with managing your personal information. \n\nChanges to this Privacy Policy \nWe reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the App or through other reasonable means. Your continued use of the App after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy. \n\nIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at skylarkh2@gmail.com.</string>
</resources>